# **ASHWIN SINGH**

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

# CONTACT

- **Q** 647-823-8722
- 🔼 Ashwin.Singh.087@gmail.com
- AshwinSingh.dev
- /in/AshwinSingh087

#### **PROFILE**

I am a detail-oriented Front-End Developer with a passion for building practical and efficient apps. My previous experience as a policy analyst and material planner allows me to take a design and build a program from the ground up, down to the last detail. My curiosity for solving problems and learning fuels my drive to write clear and concise code.

# **EDUCATION**

#### JUNO COLLEGE

OCT 2020 - JULY 2021

- Immersive Bootcamp
- Web Development & JavaScript

# SENECA COLLEGE

JAN 2017 - DEC 2017

• Government Relations

# YORK UNIVERSITY

**SEPT 2011 - JUNE 2015** 

• Kinesiology and Health Science

#### **SKILLS**







**JavaScript** 

**Firebase** 







React





**JQuery** 

#### **PROJECTS**

# NOTBLOCKBUSTER 🗹



React | Firebase | Rest API | CSS 3 | Mob Programmed Movie app built using React Router where users can explore and save movies to a filterable list connected to Firebase.

# DAILY CRYPTO UPDATE





ES6 JavaScript | SASS | Rest API | Pair Programmed Searchable cryptocurrency app, the highlighting feature is an accessible auto-suggest search bar users can select from.

# ARTIST DISCOGRAPHY [7]



React | Firebase | Rest API | HTML 5 | CSS 3 Music app which allows users to find an artist's discography and save their favorite albums to a list stored on Firebase.

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **WORK MATERIAL PLANNER**

Bombardier Aerospace | Feb 2019 - June 2020

- Worked cross-functionally with other departments including engineering and production to resolve issues and ensure deliverables were completed on time.
- Utilized SAP and Bombardier specific software to manage inventory and proactively procure required materials to assure production deadlines were met.
- Managed logistic inquiries by addressing and resolving issues that occurred, advising other departments about proper procedures and correct next steps, and expediting urgent deliverables.

# **JUNIOR POLICY ANALYST**

Ontario Public Service | Sept 2017 - Dec 2017

- Led the development of a joint ministry pilot project which included determining the approach, structuring the program, drafting all necessary documents, and facilitating the approval process with senior management.
- Liaised with other divisions and ministry partners to coordinate program development and implementation, provide opportunities for engagement and updates about recent developments on key files.